University of Connecticut 1998.0187
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
University of Connecticut, President's Office Records [Glenn W. Ferguson, 1973-1978]
undated, 1915-2005.
1998.0187
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
59.5 Linear feet
Contains the office files of the President's Office during Dr. Ferguson's administration as well as personal documents, correspondence, photographs, diaries, and emphemera from Ferguson's childhood through his careers as a diplomat, administrator of the Peace Corps/VISTA, academic administrator, and head of Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty and Lincoln Center.
University of Connecticut. President's Office.
Box 25
Box 26
Box 23
Box 24
Box 29
Box 30
Box 27
Box 28
Box 5
Box 6
Box 3
Box 4
Box 9
Box 10
Box 7
Box 8
Box 41
Box 11
Box 12
Box 13
Box 2
Box 1
Box 39
Box 45
Box 18
Box 19
Box 20
Box 21
Box 14
Box 15
Box 16
Box 17
Box 22
Box 42
Box 40
Box 44
Box 43
Box 47
Box 46
Box 32
Box 31
Box 34
Box 33
Box 36
Box 35
Box 38
Box 37
History
Glenn W. Ferguson was the ninth President of the University of Connecticut. He served from August 1973 to April 1978. His tenure occurred during a difficult period in the school's history, a period marked by financial retrenchment because of economic recession and inadequate financial support from the state legislature. The University experienced little growth during these years, but it did manage to maintain stability and quality.
A native of Syracuse, New York, Ferguson earned a bachelor's degree in economics and master's degree in business administration at Cornell University and a law degree from the University of Pittsburgh in 1957. From 1961-1969, he held various posts in the Kennedy and Johnson administrations, including Director of the Peace Corps from 1962-1964, President of VISTA from 1964-1966, United States Ambassador to Kenya from 1966-1969. In 1969, he was appointed Chancellor of Long Island University, and, from 1970-1973, was President of Clark University. In addition to his administrative posts, he also held a variety of teaching positions from 1969-1971, including Adjunct Professor of Government at Clark University and Professor of Political Science at Long Island University. Ferguson was 44 years old when he assumed the presidency of the University of Connecticut.
Total enrollment at UConn rose only slightly during Ferguson's presidency. In 1974, it cost the average resident UConn student about $2,800 per year to attend the University. By 1978, that amount had risen to $3,400. From 1975 to 1978, a time of severe inflation, the University operating budget grew by approximately thirty million dollars, while state appropriations actually declined by 2 per cent.
Despite a lack of adequate state public support, a number of major advances were made in the University's physical plant during Ferguson's tenure. Ground was broken for a new School of Fine Arts building, and the Psychology, Institute of Materials Science, and Physics buildings were completed. The Co-op bookstore was opened, as was the John N. Dempsey Hospital at the Health Center in Farmington. The crowning achievement was the completion, in 1978, of the new University of Connecticut Library, later renamed the Homer Babbidge Library.
Advances were made, as well, in both academic programs and research. During the 1973-1974 academic year, the Political Science Department created a Masters of Public Affairs degree to meet the growing demand for experts in public service and administration. In that same year, a research team from the School of Medicine announced that its vaccine against meningitis would be marketed nationally by two drug firms.
During the 1976-1977 academic year, the University admitted four students from a pilot group at the Stamford Branch that marked the formal beginning of the Bachelor if General Studies program, a degree program for non-traditional students. A Stamford grandmother was the first recipient of such a degree in 1978. The first annual Day of Pride, an event intended to inspire and encourage minority young people to pursue a college education was also held.
During the 1977-1978 school year, the University and the University of Belgrade launched a hands-across-the-sea collaboration for a scientific and educational exchange program. This was also the year that clinical certification tests of graduate students in speech pathology and audiology indicated that the University's advanced degree programs in these areas ranked in the top ten nationally.
Glenn Ferguson resigned his presidency in April 1978, in order to accept a position as Chief Executive Officer of Radio Free Europe/ Radio Liberty.
Glenn W. Ferguson died at his home in Sante Fe, New Mexico on 20 December 2007.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the administrative files of the University's office of the President during Glenn W. Ferguson's tenure from 1973-1978. Also include in this collection are the files of Ferguson's assistant, Paul Capra, as well as those of Edward Gant, who was acting president of the University for six months following Ferguson's resignation. A later addition to the collection added personal documents, correspondence, photographs, diaries, and emphemera from Ferguson's childhood through his careers as a diplomat, administrator of the Peace Corps/ VISTA, academic administrator, and head of Radio Free Europe/ Radio Liberty and Lincoln Center.
Arrangement
Series I: University Files ( 1965-1978 ) consist of communication between the President's Office and university departments and Branches; materials related to university functions, policies, and concerns; budget and financial data; committee reports; as well as general information on post-secondary education. The files are arranged alphabetically within a chronological order.
Series II: State Files ( 1974-1978 ) consist of administrative files involving the state government's interaction with the university and the state university system as a whole.
Series III: Paul Capra Papers ( 1972-1978 ) contain the files of the assistant to the president, and includes such materials as annual reports, administrative procedures, correspondence, physical plant data, and files on collective bargaining, the Storrs campus police, university finances, and research contracts.
Series IV: Edward Gant Papers ( undated ) consist of one box of materials from Edward Gant's term as acting president from August 1978 to March 1979. The materials include files on the Appropriation Committee, the capital budget, collective bargaining, the Health Center, and veterinary medicine.
Series V: Audiovisual materials ( 1975 )
Series VI: Personal Files ( 1915-2005 ) consist of personal documents, correspondence, photographs, diaries, and emphemera from Ferguson's childhood through his careers as a diplomat, administrator of the Peace Corps/VISTA, academic administrator, and head of Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty and Lincoln Center. The materials include scrapbooks, personal and professional correspondence, newspaper clippings, school work and report cards, academic notes, manuscript notes, books written by Ferguson, and emphemera.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Bibliography
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The materials were transferred to the University Archives from the President's Office.
College presidents—Connecticut.; Universities and colleges—Administration.; University of Connecticut. Office of the President.; University of Connecticut—Presidents.; Administrative Records.; Albums.; Correspondence.; Financial Records.; Minutes.; Newsletters.; Newspapers.; Notebooks.; Notes.; Photocopies.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Speeches.; Universities.
- Series I: University Files, 1965-1978
  - 1972-1973
    - A (Box 1:, Folder 1)
    - Admissions (Box 1:, Folder 2-4)
    - Affirmative Action Plan (Box 1:, Folder 5-6)
    - Agriculture, College and School of (Box 1:, Folder 7)
    - Allied health professions (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - Almuni Association (Box 1:, Folder 9)
    - Alumni correspondence and information (Box 1:, Folder 10)
    - American Council on Education (Box 1:, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report of the President to the Governor (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - Applicants (Box 1:, Folder 13-15)
    - Associated Students Commissaries (Box 1:, Folder 16)
    - Associated Student Government (Box 1:, Folder 17)
    - Association of American Colleges (Box 1:, Folder 18)
    - Association of governing boards of Universities and Colleges (Box 1:, Folder 19)
    - Athletics (Box 1:, Folder 20)
    - Auditorium (Box 1:, Folder 21)
    - B (Box 1:, Folder 22)
    - Bailey, Clark - Assistant to the President (Box 1:, Folder 23)
    - Beer Hall (Box 1:, Folder 24)
    - Black Exposition, First New England (Box 1:, Folder 25)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 1:, Folder 26)
    - Bookstore (Box 1:, Folder 27)
    - Bureau of Institutional Research (Box 1:, Folder 28)
    - Budget (Box 1:, Folder 29)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 1:, Folder 30)
    - C (Box 1:, Folder 31)
    - Campus Christian Foundation (Box 1:, Folder 32)
    - Campus Planning and Development Committee (Box 1:, Folder 33)
    - Center for Black Studies (Box 1:, Folder 34)
    - Center for Criminal Justice (proposed) (Box 1:, Folder 35)
    - Center for the Environment and Man (Box 1:, Folder 36)
    - Civil Rights (Box 1:, Folder 37)
    - Co (general) (Box 1:, Folder 38)
    - College Entrance Examination Board (Box 1:, Folder 39)
    - Commencement (Box 1:, Folder 40)
    - Commission for Higher Education (Box 1:, Folder 41)
    - Commission on Aid to Higher Education (Box 1:, Folder 43)
    - Commission on University Governance (Box 1:, Folder 44)
    - Committee Against Racism (Box 1:, Folder 45)
    - Committee for the Future (Box 1:, Folder 46)
    - Committee on the cost of Instruction, 1972-1973 (Box 1:, Folder 47)
    - Committee on Criminal Justice (Box 1:, Folder 48)
    - Committee on Curricula and Courses (Box 1:, Folder 49)
    - Committee on Scholastic Standards (Box 1:, Folder 50)
    - Committees, Standing, University (Box 1:, Folder 51)
    - Community Colleges in Connecticut (Box 1:, Folder 52)
    - Comptroller, Office of the State (Box 1:, Folder 53)
    - Computer Center (Box 1:, Folder 54)
    - Conferences (Box 1:, Folder 55)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 1:, Folder 56)
    - Connecticut Daily Campus (Box 1:, Folder 57)
    - Connecticut Higher Education TV Association (Box 1:, Folder 58)
    - Connecticut Humanities Council (Box 1:, Folder 59)
    - Connecticut Partners (Box 1:, Folder 60)
    - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council (Box 1:, Folder 61)
    - CONNPEP (Box 1:, Folder 62)
    - CONNPIRG (Box 1:, Folder 63)
    - Continuing Education Services (Box 1:, Folder 64)
    - Cooperative Extension Service (Box 1:, Folder 65)
    - Cooperative Program Planning for the New England Land-Grant Universities (Box 1:, Folder 66)
    - Council on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 1:, Folder 67)
    - E (Box 1:, Folder 68)
    - Ecological Institute (proposed) (Box 2:, Folder 69)
    - Education, School of (Box 2:, Folder 70)
    - Educational Facilities Laboratories proposal (Box 2:, Folder 71)
    - Employment authorizations (Box 2:, Folder 72)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 2:, Folder 73)
    - E.O. Smith High School (Box 2:, Folder 74)
    - Evans, Jack - Vice President for Financial Affairs (Box 2:, Folder 75)
    - F (Box 2:, Folder 76)
    - Fellowships (Box 2:, Folder 77)
    - Finance and Control Department (Box 2:, Folder 78)
    - Financial Aid Division (Box 2:, Folder 79)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 2:, Folder 80)
    - Foreign students (Box 2:, Folder 81)
    - Fraternities and sororities (Box 2:, Folder 82)
    - Gant, Edward V. (Box 2:, Folder 83-84)
    - Gerontology Program (Box 2:, Folder 85)
    - Governor's Office (Box 2:, Folder 86)
    - Graduate School (Box 2:, Folder 87)
    - Grants (Box 2:, Folder 88)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 2:, Folder 89)
    - Handicapped students, 1972-1973 (Box 2:, Folder 90)
    - Hartford Branch (Box 2:, Folder 91)
    - Hartford Training the Teachers of Teachers Center (Box 2:, Folder 92)
    - Health Center (Box 2:, Folder 93)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 2:, Folder 94)
    - Health Service Advisory Attorney (Box 2:, Folder 95)
    - Homecoming day 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 96)
    - Home Economics, School of (Box 2:, Folder 97)
    - Honors (Box 2:, Folder 98)
    - Housing and Food Services (Box 2:, Folder 99)
    - I (Box 2:, Folder 100)
    - Invitations (Box 2:, Folder 101)
    - L (Box 2:, Folder 102)
    - Lakeside Apartments reservations (Box 2:, Folder 103)
    - Legislative (Box 2:, Folder 104)
    - Liberal Arts and Sciences, College of (Box 2:, Folder 105)
    - Loeb Awards, 1965-1973 (Box 2:, Folder 106)
    - M (Box 2:, Folder 107)
    - Mansfield (Box 2:, Folder 108)
    - Master plan (Box 2:, Folder 109)
    - McMahon Lecture (Box 2:, Folder 110)
    - Museum of Art - Paul Rovetti, Director (Box 2:, Folder 111)
    - N (Box 2:, Folder 112)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (Box 2:, Folder 113)
    - Newcomer's Tea (Box 2:, Folder 114)
    - New England Center for Continuing Education (Box 2:, Folder 115)
    - New England Regional Student Program (Box 2:, Folder 116)
    - New England Universities Children Exchange Program (Box 2:, Folder 117)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 2:, Folder 118)
    - P (Box 2:, Folder 119)
    - Pharmacy, School of (Box 2:, Folder 120)
    - President's Emeritus Tea (Box 2:, Folder 121)
    - Project Leadership (Box 2:, Folder 122)
    - R (Box 2:, Folder 123)
    - Receipts, liquor (Box 2:, Folder 124)
    - Red Cross Bloodmobile (Box 2:, Folder 125)
    - Religious Counselors Luncheon (Box 2:, Folder 126)
    - Resolutions on fiscal controls (Box 2:, Folder 127)
    - Revitalization Corps (Box 2:, Folder 128)
    - Rohrbach, John G. - Assistant Vice-President (Box 2:, Folder 129)
    - S (Box 2:, Folder 130)
    - Shea, Gail - Women's Advocate, Provost's Office (Box 2:, Folder 131)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 2:, Folder 132)
    - Southeastern Branch, 1972-1973 (Box 2:, Folder 133)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 2:, Folder 134)
    - Student affairs (Box 2:, Folder 135)
    - Student Senate (Box 2:, Folder 136)
    - Student Union Board of Governors (Box 2:, Folder 137)
    - Summer Seminar of the Institute of World Affairs (Box 2:, Folder 138)
    - T (Box 2:, Folder 139)
    - Traffic and Parking, Advisory Committee (Box 2:, Folder 140)
    - Trustee/Administration/Faculty/Student Committee (Box 2:, Folder 141)
    - W (Box 2:, Folder 142)
    - WHUS (Box 2:, Folder 143)
    - Women's concerns (Box 2:, Folder 144)
    - Y (Box 2:, Folder 145)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 2:, Folder 146)
  - 1973-1974
    - Accounts receivable, 1973-1974 (Box 3:, Folder 147)
    - Accreditation (Box 3:, Folder 148)
    - Affirmative Action Program (Box 3:, Folder 149)
    - Agriculture, U.S. Department of (Box 3:, Folder 150)
    - Allied Health Professions (Box 3:, Folder 151-152)
    - American Association for Higher Education (Box 3:, Folder 153)
    - American Association of State Colleges and Universities (Box 3:, Folder 154)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 3:, Folder 155)
    - American Association of University Women (Box 3:, Folder 156)
    - American Council on Education (Box 3:, Folder 157)
    - Appeals (Box 3:, Folder 158)
    - Applicants (Box 3:, Folder 159-162)
    - Appropriations Committee of the General Assembly (Box 3:, Folder 163)
    - Association of American Colleges (Box 3:, Folder 164)
    - Association of Governing Boards (Box 3:, Folder 165)
    - Auditorium, Albert N. Jorgensen (Box 3:, Folder 166)
    - Auditorium Search Committee (Box 3:, Folder 167)
    - Auerbach Service Bureau for Connecticut Organizations (Box 3:, Folder 168)
    - Auxiliary Services Fund (Box 3:, Folder 169)
    - Bartlett Arboretum (Box 3:, Folder 170)
    - Black students (Box 3:, Folder 171-172)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 3:, Folder 173)
    - Bookstore (Box 3:, Folder 174-175)
    - Branches, University of Connecticut (Box 3:, Folder 176)
    - Campus Community Carnival (Box 4:, Folder 177)
    - Center for the Environment and Man (Box 4:, Folder 178)
    - Christmas card list (Box 4:, Folder 179)
    - College Entrance Exam Board, 1973-1974 (Box 4:, Folder 180)
    - Commencement - convocation (Box 4:, Folder 181-182)
    - Commendations and complaints (Box 4:, Folder 183)
    - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 4:, Folder 184)
    - Comptroller, Office of the State (Box 4:, Folder 185)
    - Connecticut Civil Liberties Union (CCLU) (Box 4:, Folder 186)
    - Connecticut Daily Campus (Box 4:, Folder 187)
    - Connecticut Labor Department (Box 4:, Folder 188)
    - CONNFACTS (Box 4:, Folder 189)
    - CONNPEP (Box 4:, Folder 190)
    - CONNPIRG (Box 4:, Folder 191)
    - Connecticut Public Television (Box 4:, Folder 192)
    - Connecticut State Employee Association (CSEA) (Box 4:, Folder 193)
    - CONNTAC (Box 4:, Folder 194)
    - Council for Moral Leadership (Box 4:, Folder 195)
    - Day care for children (Box 4:, Folder 196)
    - Eastern States Exposition (Box 4:, Folder 197)
    - Education abstracts ( American College Public Relations Association) (Box 4:, Folder 198)
    - Education, State Department of (Box 4:, Folder 199)
    - Educational associations (Box 4:, Folder 200)
    - Emeritus staff (Box 4:, Folder 201)
    - Energy crisis (Box 4:, Folder 202)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity (Box 4:, Folder 203-204)
    - Faculty for Rational Alternatives (Box 4:, Folder 205)
    - Federation of University Teachers (Box 4:, Folder 206)
    - Ferguson, Glenn W. (Box 4:, Folder 207-206)
    - Film programs (Box 4:, Folder 207)
    - Fraternities and sororities (Box 4:, Folder 208)
    - General (Box 4:, Folder 209-211)
    - Gerontology (Box 4:, Folder 212)
    - Governor's office - Thomas Meskill (Box 4:, Folder 213)
    - Grievance procedure (Box 4:, Folder 214)
    - Handicapped students (Box 4:, Folder 215)
    - Hartford Branch (Box 4:, Folder 216)
    - Health Center (Box 5:, Folder 217-218)
    - Health, Education & Welfare, U.S. Department of (Box 5:, Folder 219)
    - Heart Tea (Box 5:, Folder 220)
    - Homecoming Letter (Box 5:, Folder 221)
    - Honors program (Box 5:, Folder 222)
    - Hopkins, Thomas (Box 5:, Folder 223)
    - Institute of International and Intercultural Studies (phase out) (Box 5:, Folder 224)
    - Insurance, School of (Box 5:, Folder 225)
    - Invitations (Box 5:, Folder 226-227)
    - Joint Operations Committee - Land Grant Universities of New England, 1973-1974 (Box 5:, Folder 228)
    - Lakeside Apartments (Box 5:, Folder 229)
    - Law, School of (Box 5:, Folder 230-232)
    - Legislative concerns (Box 5:, Folder 233)
    - Legislature's Intern Program (Box 5:, Folder 234)
    - Loeb Awards - correspondence (Box 5:, Folder 235)
    - Mansfield Town Council (Box 5:, Folder 236)
    - Massachusetts, University of - collective bargaining (Box 6:, Folder 237)
    - McMahon Lecture (Box 6:, Folder 238)
    - Media (Box 6:, Folder 239)
    - Medicine, School of Dental (Box 6:, Folder 240)
    - Medicine, School of (Box 6:, Folder 241-245)
    - Minority statistics (Box 6:, Folder 246)
    - Museum of Art: Paul Rovetti, Dir. (Box 6:, Folder 247)
    - NAACP (Box 6:, Folder 248-250)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (Box 6:, Folder 251-253)
    - New England Center for Continuing Education (Box 6:, Folder 254-255)
    - New England College presidents (Box 6:, Folder 256)
    - New England Council on Continuing Education (Box 6:, Folder 257)
    - New England Faculty Children Exchange Program (Box 6:, Folder 258)
    - New England Land Grant Universities (Box 6:, Folder 259)
    - Northeast Regional Center for Rural Development (Box 6:, Folder 260)
    - NOW - National Organization for Women (Box 6:, Folder 261)
    - Organization of faculty and Professional Women (Box 6:, Folder 262)
    - Organization for Tropical Studies (Box 6:, Folder 263)
    - PEFCO - Private Export Funding Corporation (Box 7:, Folder 264)
    - President's annual report (Box 7:, Folder 265)
    - President's Emeritus Tea (Box 7:, Folder 266)
    - Professional Employee Association (Box 7:, Folder 267-268)
    - Promotion - tenure (Box 7:, Folder 269)
    - Property negotiations (Box 7:, Folder 270)
    - Public Information Office (Box 7:, Folder 271)
    - Racism (Box 7:, Folder 272-273)
    - Radio-Television Center (Box 7:, Folder 274)
    - Red Cross Bloodmobile (Box 7:, Folder 275)
    - Religion (Box 7:, Folder 276)
    - Retirement (Box 7:, Folder 277)
    - ROTC (Box 7:, Folder 278)
    - Sabbatical Leave (Box 7:, Folder 279)
    - Salaries (Box 7:, Folder 280)
    - Scholarships and gifts (Box 7:, Folder 281)
    - Senate, University, 1973-1974 (Box 7:, Folder 282-289)
    - Sit in, Wilbur Cross Library (Box 7:, Folder 290)
    - Sloan, Alfred P., Foundation (Box 7:, Folder 291)
    - Social Work, School of - Morton Coleman, Dean (Box 7:, Folder 292)
    - Southeastern Branch (Box 7:, Folder 293)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 7:, Folder 294-295)
    - State colleges (Box 8:, Folder 296)
    - State government (Box 8:, Folder 297)
    - State of Connecticut - Board for State Academic Awards (Box 8:, Folder 298)
    - TAFS Committee (Box 8:, Folder 299)
    - Telephone (Box 8:, Folder 300)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 8:, Folder 301)
    - Travel (Box 8:, Folder 302)
    - U.S. Department of Labor (Box 8:, Folder 303)
    - Universities (Box 8:, Folder 304)
    - University Chronicle (Box 8:, Folder 305)
    - University Computer Center (Box 8:, Folder 306)
    - University of Connecticut Summer Program (Box 8:, Folder 307)
    - Veterinary Medicine Program (Box 8:, Folder 308)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 8:, Folder 309)
    - WHUS (Box 8:, Folder 310)
    - Women's concerns (Box 8:, Folder 311)
    - Women's Council (Box 8:, Folder 312)
    - Women's Studies Program (Box 8:, Folder 313)
    - Zarrow Scholarship Fund (Box 8:, Folder 314)
  - 1974-1975
    - Activities, Connecticut Legislatures (Box 8:, Folder 315)
    - Ad hoc Committee on Legislative Matters (Box 8:, Folder 316)
    - Admissions (Box 8:, Folder 317)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 8:, Folder 318)
    - Agriculture's Engineering Lab (Box 8:, Folder 319)
    - Allowances, representation (Box 8:, Folder 320)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 8:, Folder 321)
    - American Association of University Teachers (Box 8:, Folder 322)
    - Annual reports of other institutions (Box 8:, Folder 323)
    - Annual reports (Box 8:, Folder 324-327)
    - August, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 328)
    - Chronicle: Surveys and Studies (Box 8:, Folder 329)
    - Correspondence (Box 8:, Folder 330-331)
    - Ferguson's appointment to presidency (newspaper clips) (Box 8:, Folder 332)
    - Grants (Box 8:, Folder 333)
    - Health and safety, public (Box 9:, Folder 334)
    - Inauguration invitations, 1974-1975 (Box 9:, Folder 335)
    - Legislature 1973 - Nurses (Box 9:, Folder 336)
    - Loeb Award (Box 9:, Folder 337-340)
    - New England State Universities (Box 9:, Folder 341)
    - Printed item (Box 9:, Folder 342)
    - Public works (Box 9:, Folder 343)
    - Sick leave, vacation - professional staff (Box 9:, Folder 344)
    - Sleeman, Phillip J., Director, AV Center (Box 9:, Folder 345-347)